at the time of this recording it's 2025
and everybody in their mother is looking
for different ways on how to make money
outside of the traditional route having
to go to school having to get a degree
and having to work a 9 to5 which people
are now realizing that they're
exchanging a lot of their time for a
very little amount of money people are
realizing that there's other
Alternatives out there and following the
traditional route is not going to give
them the life that they want now I'm not
like other people out there that are
completely against colleges and
completely against the school system I
personally support it I believe that we
need doctors that go and study medicine
so they're able to take care of six
people I believe that we need Engineers
so they are constantly studying and
innovating on how to create new
buildings and roads I believe we need
lawyers and I believe we need scientists
so law is continuously respected and
healthc care and medicine is constantly
innovating the school system is created
for those that want a secure and
guaranteed income which there is nothing
wrong with that because these people are
happy in their N9 to- FS they're happy
in their routine and they're happy being
secure they don't have to worry about
doing nothing other than going to their
job completing their work and going back
home some people find a lot of pleasure
in that and those people will not be
watching this video you're watching this
video because you are skeptical of
entering this world or you have been in
this world and you want to break out of
it and you want to find a different
alternative on how to live your dream
life because you're either going to
spend years getting a degree that you
will truthfully never use and you're
going to end up at a job which is that
what you envision yourself to be doing
and as you're in this job you're not
feeling how you thought you would feel
after years of school after hundreds of
thousand in depth and truthfully not
living the life that you want to live
because now you're living for this job
so you have this guaranteed income
you're here because you want something
better and you know there's something
better and there's nothing against the
school system because there's people out
there that are very happy with their the
way their life
but not you you want something better
and you know that you're capable of
doing it and there's a different route
on how for you to get it now obviously
there is exceptions out there let's say
you take path a where you would go to
college you would get a degree you would
get a job if you are really dedicated to
your craft and you really deeply love it
and you see an opportunity for
Innovation and you want to be better you
will then figure out a way on how to
make a business out of it and how to
create different sources of income
around it but the majority of people are
scared of taking risk are scared to
putting at jeery their security from
this job and truthfully don't want to
lose time or money so the majority of
them just stay in the exact same spot
and just wait enough time in order for
them to get a promotion or wait for a
window to open so they make money on
overtime now those people that really
Excel onto the next level it's really
all up to them and how optimistic they
are and now let's put into example path
B where you ended up either going to
college and getting a degree that really
did nothing for you or you didn't end up
getting a degree at all now you're
probably in a very mid to average job
paying you minimum wage or a little bit
more and it's not enough for you and not
making ends me now you might think that
just because you're in this position
that you will never be successful and
that's actually not the truth there is
many cases out there how somebody can go
into a rest restaurant and just be
someone helping in the kitchen they find
a lot of passion for making this food
and they decide that now they're going
to take risk and go open their own
restaurant and as soon as they open this
restaurant it's a hit because they're
passionate about it they love what they
do and they're taking risk being
Innovative and are very dedicated to it
but again this is very small percentage
like it if you're in path a or in path B
it's a very specific and Elite type of
person that gets to this point but for
the rest they are always constantly
looking for a different way on how to
make money I have personally never met
anybody that is in a secure and
guaranteed income after somebody that
graduated college that does not look for
a different way on how to make money a
new way on how to add a source of income
for them without them putting at
Jeopardy their guaranteed source of
income and the same thing goes for those
that did not go to college and have an
average job they're constantly always
finding new ways on how to get an added
source of income so whether you went on
path a or whether you went on path B
they both ended up in the exact same
spot you end up in a video like this
trying to find a new way on how to make
money online or how to make any type of
money outside of what you currently do
so if you chose path a your path B on
path a you are in $100,000 of depth
years loss by getting experience and
knowledge that do nothing for you and if
you went on path B you wasted time at a
job that you probably never loved and
just did it for the money and you never
really learned the skill set and you
ended up at the exact same spot so
whether you're on path a or path B
you're still looking for the same
solution and this is the harsh reality
somebody that can study 6 years to
become a nurse after them graduating and
working at a hospital for 2 3 years they
end up not liking it but they end up
feeling in depth with themselves with
their family with their colleagues where
they have to stay at that job to now pay
back the depth of these six years but
they're going to keep looking for
different ways on how to get out of that
job because just inside of them they
can't Envision themselves working here
for the next 30 years until they could
retire because those first 10 years
alone is just to pay back the student
debt and somebody on path B where they
did not go to college at all they're
working at a very average job they
literally living paycheck to paycheck
and they're not happy at all with their
lives and they're almost regretting that
they didn't go to college and pursue
something so they could have made a
better income for themselves thinking
that if they would have gone to college
they would have had a better outcome but
little do they know that both people are
in the exact same spot some studied more
others worked more and they both want
the same thing a different way on how to
make money online and the easiest
alternative to making more money
is going online nobody thinks for them
to make more money they have to work
harder they understand that for them to
actually live the life that they want
they have to stop exchanging time for
money their time is the most valuable
asset that they have and if they're
constantly clocking in somewhere and
they're losing anywhere from 8 to 9
hours of their day they're only left
with so much more time for them to
become a better person so people
understand order for them to become more
successful and make more money they have
to go online online has been the
craziest land of opportunity where
people that have gone on path a have
studied and hated their job ended up
leaving and becoming successful and you
have people on path B that didn't go to
college don't know anything about school
and found the niche and they ended up
making millions online online is the
land of opportunity and I'm not talking
about creating a e-commerce store where
you have to buy stuff from online and
resell them online that's burnt out the
opportunity there is really not it I'm
not talking about creating your own
marketing agency where you have to
constantly be scaling and selling
yourself and looking for different
people to Market stuff for them and deal
with them and then hire people I'm not
talking you create your own product or
your own brand where you have to create
your own designs hire a team and invest
money in order for you to maybe see
something in return I'm not talking any
of these things online and I'm
definitely not talking about creating
something super Innovative like new
Facebook or a new app going online you
don't have to create something new from
scratch using everything that's out
there with a profitable skill set is
more than enough to make millions
without you having to create anything on
your own you just use what's already out
there for your benefit I became
extremely successful and how I've made
over $20 million at the age of 24 is by
learning a skill set and by using what's
out there on the internet I have not
created anything I haven't even used AI
in my advantage I'm doing it old school
learning what's out there putting it
together and making it something and
it's trading I'm going to tell you
straight up how it is I'm not going to
convince you that I have some
state-of-the-art advanced technology or
something that I found in the back of a
book or something that I heard in a
meeting with millionaires no I figured
out how to create an edge in the markets
when I would go trade and I've been
doing this consistently for the last 6
years and it has made me Millions
without me having to hire a team without
me having to speak to anybody without me
having to leave my house I've made $20
million in my underwear from the office
of my home as a 24-year-old that did not
go to college and just 7 years ago was
working at Dunkin' Donuts if you don't
think it's possible I don't know what
else to tell you and to be fully
transparent and be as real and raw as it
gets that's exactly what this video is
about this video is about trading I'm
going to tell you exactly what trading
really is after 7 years in the markets
as a 24y old I'm going to tell you what
it's not and what critics out there make
it seem to be and the reality of how
your trading is going to be just because
I became a millionaire does it mean that
you are is the opportunity for you to
become a millionaire there yes but only
if you do the right steps and now don't
get me wrong some people just want to
make enough money so so they leave their
job let's say you're making 5 6K a month
they just want to make that so they
don't have to go back to work and maybe
they aspire to make a little bit more
like $110,000 a month which is every
person's first goal to feel like they're
very successful and truthfully I thought
that was enough too at first but then
when you spend more time in it and you
see the more opportunities that
continues to raise and raise and raise
very fast and now I'm at the point where
I want it all but the opportunity is for
you to set your your own cap on how much
you want to make and on how fast you
want to get there you're not being
capped by a system or by somebody that
doesn't let you get to the next level
you are the person that is going to let
yourself get to that next level or not
I'm going to explain all of that in this
video and I want to emphasize the impact
and the importance of this opportunity
with the skill set that I'm about to
teach you this is pandemic proof this is
Recession Proof this is any economical
situation proof this is an opportunity
that doesn't matter where you are in the
world you're going to be able to make
money no matter what it is something
that's going to be automated into your
lifestyle and is fully dependent on you
if you want to make money you will if
you don't want to make money you won't
it's never going to go out of style and
it's never going to be forgotten and now
I'm going to ask you a question do you
remember your life before you knew how
to walk do you remember your life before
you knew how to talk no right because
you've been doing it for so long that it
just became part of your life it's made
you who you are this video is going to
do the exact same thing inside of this
video I'm going to open up something in
your mind where it's going to completely
change the Journey of your life your
mind now is going to be curious on how
can you unlock this skill set in order
for you to actually live the life that
you want to live get out of the job that
you're currently in I'm going to unlock
this drive and C osity that you were
born with you just needed a video like
this to give you a reality check and let
you know that you're capable of doing it
you just need somebody to show you how
to do it now this is what I'm going to
be offering you I'm going to teach you
exactly how you can earn the money and
where does it even come from because
obviously money doesn't come from thin
air and nobody is going to be just
giving you money because you're going to
trade there's a lot of conspiracy
theories around this is the money even
real since it's digital and believe me
the money is real I'm going to teach you
exactly about that I'm going to teach
you exactly what a profitable skill set
in trading is and what is not because
people think just because a chart is
going up you should buy or because a
chart is going down you should sell that
is not how these things work that is not
how I became successful in trading I'm
going to teach you exactly how to do it
I'm going to explain to you the most
common scams in the industry there's a
lot of people out here that get
convinced that they're going to to be
rich overnight and I'm sadly here to
tell you that you're not you have the
opportunity to be successful if you put
in the work if you don't you simply
won't be there's no getrich quick scheme
and I am not guaranteeing you anything
remotely near that if you don't put in
the work you will not be successful I'm
going to be breaking down and exposing
on why trading is the most profitable
and easiest skill set to obtain for
anybody around the world doesn't matter
your age doesn't matter your level of
knowledge and it does not matter how
much time you have available to this
skill set trailing caters to absolutely
everybody that really wants to learn it
and truthfully the most important thing
I'm going to be teaching you how you can
learn so you can start making money in
2025 with the exact same skill set that
made me over $20 million in the last 7
years of my trading career and oh boy
has it been a bumpy journey and before
we get started and I give you context on
everything I just mentioned you're
probably wondering who is this guy and
why should I even listen to him is he
even credible well my name is Alex G and
if you don't know who I am I am a
24-year-old Trader born and raised in
Miami that just wanted to be very
successful and he did not want to let
his path to be successful effect on how
he lived his life and I Liv my life
pretty lavishly you probably seen me r r
on the Super Bowl why because why not
you probably seen me do donuts and
Bugattis and my Lambos pores why because
why not you've probably seen me do a lot
of things that a regular successful
person won't do because they're very
uptight and want to be corporately and
publicly seen correct not me I am very
successful and I'm very happy with my
current state because I'm myself I don't
let the money change who I am and I
don't let the money Define who I am I am
who I am the money just gives me access
to better toys and do funner things but
I will never let the money change who I
am or Define it so I am Alex G a 24
yearold Trader that likes to make a [__]
ton of money and live lavish and that's
just my public resume this is just the
life that I like to live with the
results that I get from Trading but when
it comes to trading I've done many
legendary challenges and stuff that I
personally never thought I'd be able to
achieve I've turned $100 into a million
in 90 days I've had half a million doll
days I've streamed for 48 hours in front
of tens of thousands of people showing
my trades live where I was turning
$400,000 into a million truthfully I've
done more than I expected that I would
be doing at the age of 24 and even
something that I don't really like to
brag about I have traveled around the
whole entire world teaching hundreds
thousands of people showing them this
skill set in person shaking their hand
completely for free and give them
context on what trading is and how it
can change your lives why did I do this
truthfully because I love what I do and
I did all of this completely for free
and as time went on hundreds of
thousands of people started following me
and were willing to pay me for my
knowledge and I was almost shocked
because I didn't know the impact that
was made making on people that's where I
ended up making a community where now we
have tens of thousands of students all
around the world enjoying the fruits of
the labor of following this strategy a
strategy that I personally made by
myself after being a negative and
unprofitable Trader for a little over 2
years because at the beginning of my
journey I did not make any money I was
actually a consistently unprofitable
Trader for nearly 2 years after I
finally figured out how to make an edge
and then had actually become a
profitable Trader so this is a very
over-the-top explanation on who I am and
how I got here and how I am qualified
and valid to be teaching you this new
skill set that you're going to obtain
and be executing in 2025 so I'm going to
start off with the most obvious what
trading is not trading is not a scam
trading is not Bitcoin trading you're
not actually Trading or exchanging
something you're not actually buying or
owning anything you're not actually
selling anything you're not actually
really doing anything other than just
betting so Bitcoin is its own crypto
currency stocks are their own individual
markets then you have Futures indices
then you have what I do currency trading
when you're currency trading you're
trading one currency versus the other
for example Euro USD you're trading the
euro versus the dollar or dollar versus
the Euro so Euro USD is just like
Muhammad Ali and Mike Tyson Muhammad Ali
and Mike Tyson are in a fight sometimes
Muhammad is winning sometimes Mike is
winning and the battle goes back and
forth same thing on Euro USD sometime
the Euro gets stronger sometime the
dollar gets stronger they're constantly
in a fight back and forth now the only
difference in between these two is that
Muhammad Ali and Mike Tyson get tired
and they have to take a break and the
fight comes to an end and there's a
winner when it comes to the markets they
never get tired they never stop and
there's never a winner markets are
constantly fighting up and down and all
you simply have to do is BET which one
is going to get stronger and it can be
for a very short period of time it can
be for a longer period of time or it can
be for a very very long period of time
you define on how long that period is
going to be for example you can bet that
Mike Tyson is going to beat Muhammad Ali
in the next 30 minutes or in the next
hour or 2 hours that his points will be
higher than Muhammad's in x amount of
time do that exact same thing but with
the markets and the markets Never End
never close and there is thousands of
different markets out there meaning the
opportunity ities are absolutely endless
and that's actually what trading is when
you're betting on Muhammad Ali and Mike
Tyson at no point do you ever own a
piece of Muhammad Ali or Mike Tyson that
would be insane same thing when you're
trading the markets when you buy a
market or sell a market at any given
point are you ever actually owning any
Euro or selling any dollar you're just
betting that the market is going to
either go up or go down and keep in mind
since the markets are never ending
you're never late to entering the market
it's not like a fight in Muhammad Ali or
Mike Tyson that there's five rounds of 5
minutes each for example you have only a
certain period of time to enter a bet
before the fight's over and then you
lose out on your opportunity in the
markets you're never late whether you
start right now whether you start at an
hour and a month in a year you're never
late the opportunities are always there
because the markets are always open and
that's really what trading is trading is
not a pyramid scheme trading is not
multi-level marketing trading is not a
software or an automation bot that will
trade for you trading is when you bet
that something is going to go up or that
something is going to go down trading
you can do from anywhere in the world
you just need a computer and Wi-Fi that
is simply it you don't need to enter in
a call with people you don't need to
hire somebody you don't need to have a
manager you don't need to have a
supervisor you don't need to have a boss
you don't need to have anything it's
just you and the charts so at this point
like wow that's pretty easy what do I
need to actually start trading well I'm
going to tell you what you don't need
you don't need a college degree you
don't need to be good at math for some
very odd reason people think you need to
be good at math to trade I don't know
why at no given point are you ever doing
any complex equations or any equations
at all you don't need to keep up with
the news or constantly be on top of the
newspaper and reading articles all of
that is simply a waste of time and the
last and the one that drives me the
craziest you do not need to be in front
of the computer all day in order for you
to make money and become a profitable
Trader all you need to actually trade
the market is going to be a computer a
couple hundred bucks to trade because
truthfully you need money to make money
this is not something that's going to
come out of thin air you need Wi-Fi and
you need anywhere from 1 to 2 hours
every single day now the key with those
1 to two hours is not whenever you are
available it's whenever the markets are
in the right trading sessions in order
for you to trade and the most important
above all is a winning strategy you can
have everything that I just mentioned
but if you don't have a strategy you
will not be successful you're going to
simply just waste time and waste a lot
of your money and the best analogy that
I can for this is imagine you're going
head-to-head with Mike Tyson you know
all the rules of the game you know that
you're going to be wearing gloves you
know you can't be throwing kicks you
know there's certain rounds but you
haven't been training and you don't have
any stamina and you don't have any
punching power or any practice what's
going to happen Mike Tyson is going to
knock you the [__] out the markets will
do the exact same thing to you if you do
not have a winning strategy this is so
key to longevity and becoming a
profitable Trader and now knowing that
the strategy is the most important thing
I'm going to explain to you how mine
works mine lets me make anywhere from
300 to even
$700,000 in one single week at a time
now my strategy consists of three very
strong very simple but extremely key
foundations in trading as a whole and if
I don't have one I can't move on to the
next let me explain the first thing of
my strategy is going to be the trend if
the trend is not in my favor I cannot
execute a trade let me give you an
example if the market is heading to the
upside I should only be looking for buys
if the market is heading to the downside
I should only be looking for sales for
some reason a lot of beginner Traders or
even intermediate Traders they believe
because the market has hit a low that
they should buy there because the market
has to go up or because the market has
hit a high that they should sell there
because the market has to come back down
and this could be nothing further from
the truth and this is where 99% of
Traders will make their first fatal
mistake on having a profitable strategy
like mine because the key to this is
trading with the trend the trend is your
friend and the best analogy I can put
with this is a surfer if I am a surfer
my job as a Surfer is to go to the beach
get into the ocean let a wave arise and
I surf the wave if the wave is heading
east to Shore and I want to go west
what's going to happen I'm surfing
against the wave so I'm going to
probably fall and get eaten by a shark
the easiest thing is to surf the wave
East as it's going that is the exact
same thing with the markets if the
markets are all heading to the upside
why do I want to do the complete
opposite I'm going to risk money that I
shouldn't and I'm going to lose so I
simply continue to trade with the trend
and follow its direction this is the
first step in my strategy and it is the
most fundamental and important because
if I don't have the trend then I can't
go into the next step which is going to
be the area of Interest now the area of
interest is as important as the trend
because once again let's say you're a
surfer and you're out in the ocean and
there is loads of waves and as soon as
this wave approaches you if you don't
have a specific area where you're going
to enter this wave two things are going
to happen you're either going to enter
too early or too late which ultimately
means that you missed the wave and you
couldn't ride the wave to the shore it's
the exact same thing in trading it's the
exact same thing with my strategy I can
have the trend in my favor but if I
don't have a very specific and detailed
area of Interest I can completely miss a
trade a trade can either have a move too
early or too late if I don't place the
area of Interest correctly so you can
even be in the right direction of the
market but if you don't have the area of
interest you don't have a trade so now
in the event that let's say you do have
a perfect area of interest and now price
is there then comes the final and most
important step and just like the last
one if you don't have the trade at the
area of interest you cannot then go to
the third step which which is the entry
signal so right back to the surfing
analogy you can have the waves going
east in your direction you can have the
entry point right where you're going to
enter the wave but if you're not on your
board properly if you don't have the
strap tight around your foot you simply
cannot enter that wave you're not ready
to enter at that area of interest
because you can either fall and lose
your board same exact thing happens in
the markets you can have the trend in
your favor you can have the area of
interest but if the market does not
present to you the entry signal at the
area of interest you simply do not take
a trade every single step is a chain
reaction you need one to have the other
to have the other and all three of those
collectively together give you a very
high probability trade setup which gives
you more odds of winning than losing now
when you surf a wave you're going to
fall it's part of the process when you
trade you're going to lose it's part of
the process what the strategy does is it
minimizes the amount of times you lose
and maximizes the amount of times you
win so to summarize the strategy
consists of trend area of interest and
entry signal you need each one to go to
the next one and I will never take a
trade unless I have all three of them
thanks to that I've been able to make
over $20 million in the markets and you
have somebody like Mike for example that
they have become a six figure Trader
thanks to following the strategy by just
following it in 6 months and you have
somebody like Alec which he was a
full-time worker and then he actually
ended up becoming a six-figure Trader as
he had a full-time job because the
strategy gives you the opportunity for
you to actually be able to work your job
and execute the trades in the markets at
the same time because you only need
anywhere from 1 to 2 hours every single
day to be trading you don't have to be
stuck in front of the computer all day
and at this point you're probably asking
yourself a question is it even worth it
for me to actually get into this skill
set and get involved into trading I've
heard it's very risky I've heard a lot
of people have lost money in it can I
even become successful well let me
explain one of the very cool and main
reasons you should is because of the
geographical Freedom you have you can
trade from anywhere in the world all you
need is a laptop and Wi-Fi
and let's be honest 99% of the places
where you could go in the world will let
you have your laptop and will let you
get access to Wi-Fi so you can connect
to the markets at any given point in
addition to that depending where you are
in the world certain trading sessions
are in your advantage the odds of you
becoming successful in trading are a lot
higher than people in certain parts of
the world for example for me it is very
hard for me to trade one of the highest
volume sessions called London session
because it's in the middle of the night
for me it initiates at 2: in the morning
but for example somebody in London it's
the middle of the day for them 10: in
the morning and they could very easily
access it so it's something that you
have great advantage or maybe even a
disadvantage based off of where you are
in the world but the beauty of it is
that you can access it from wherever and
whenever you want so if you're not in
London and you want to trade in the
mornings you can just get on a quick
flight and you're there and you trade
from there you're not attached to an
office you're not attached to a machine
you're not attached to a boss you're not
attached to a system it's whenever you
want to access it and it is accessible
24/7 from wherever in the world from
your phone from your laptop from your
Apple watch from your desktop and
truthfully once you become a Trader
traveling around the world becomes
essentially free you're a Trader you
make a lot of money you can go anywhere
you want gives you the freedom of you
being able to to do whatever you want
I've been able to travel over 15
different countries in the span of just
one single year and I only get oneway
flights I get a oneway I get an Airbnb
and when I'm ready to leave I leave to
the next spot I don't have anybody
telling me when to go back I don't have
to go back I do whatever I want when I
want and that ties into how much money
you will even make as you travel to
different places in the world you start
opening your eyes to different Visions
to different traditions different
cultures which will ultimately make you
more money because your mindset is being
open to something new and you put the
cap on how much you want to make there
is an infinite access to how much money
you can make in the markets just depends
on when you're ready to click that buy
or click that sell button however other
business models don't get anywhere near
on how profitable trading is for example
e-commerce crypto Airbnb management
smma and even personal brand development
have no comparison to The Leverage you
could have from Trading alone let me
break it down if you were to create an
Ecom store you have a starting capital
of anywhere from
$5,000 and your margins depending on how
good you are could be anywhere from 15
to 30% and what you need to start in
order for you to earn money is a lot you
have to create a store you have to get a
business you have to get a credit card
you have to get employees a team do
market research you need a lot of things
in order for you to be successful and
the risk associated with this is very
high and a lot of them get shut down
because they don't even know how to
properly run ads and Facebook just ends
up closing it down because they see it
as a very high-risk business or maybe
even a scam and the scalability of it is
somewhat medium where you are able to
scale if you can properly make it out
but truthfully it's actually very
difficult crypto on the other hand has a
very different different starting
Capital could be anywhere from ,000 to
about $10,000 the benefit of it is that
you have 100% margin because you don't
really have to pay anybody you're just
investing into some coins and
realistically just hoping that it gets
up what you need to get started is
really nothing other than your computer
and this is the closest one that gets
the trading but the reality of the
situation is that it is nothing compared
to it because what you need to succeed
is somewhat luck Market vol aity and
very very very deep investigation on the
right coins the risk associated with
crypto is extremely high and then you're
actually buying something you're
obtaining it and you're holding it for
longer periods of time scalability is
high but it is very very risky Airbnb
management I personally know from
personal experience starting capital is
a very very low minimum of $5,000 and
can scale way past $100,000 margins if
you're good and you have really really
lucky months can be as high as 40% but a
very very low average is 15% what you
need in order to actually make a lot of
money with Airbnb management is a lot
you need a good marketer you need a good
content creator you need a very good
cleaning lady and you personally need a
very good location in hopes that the
algorithm in Airbnb will list your
property the risk associated is very
high because you either have to sign a
lease do rental Arbitrage or even buy
your own property not even knowing if
people would want to rent it out and the
scalability is extremely low because you
could only buy so many properties at a
time and you can only manage so many
properties at a time next we have smma
which starting Capital truthfully is
nothing you just need a decent amount of
knowledge for you to be able to actually
get your first clients and be able to
manage them margins can be nowhere from
30 to 60% just depends on how good this
brand is it's going to require a lot of
your time and you will definitely hit a
cap simply because you can only scale so
much by the knowledge that you have and
the risk associated with this is very
high along with reputational costs
because a lot of brands do not let your
skills enough time in order for them to
actually flourish and scalability like I
just mentioned is very low because
truthfully you can only manage so many
people because you only have so many
hours in the day before you burn out and
next we have personal brand which many
think is a great skill set which it is
but there's a lot of Cons with it the
starting capital is anywhere from ,000
to
$5,000 and you really just have to
invest in a camera and in your
self-confidence a lot of people out
there they really don't want to be in
front of the camera because they just
want to make money by M themselves and
live their life privately the benefits
of it is you will keep 100% margin
because whatever you make yourself off
of your brand you simply keep and what
you need in order to make money is a lot
more than even a business you need to
have an idea you need to have a strategy
need to have content editors marketers
thumbnail creators script writers
copywriters editors there's so much
required to building a personal brand
that the risk associated with it isn't
High because the only thing that you're
putting at risk is just your name but
the scalability is very low unless you
have a big team and big ideas and Big
Marketing it is very hard to make it and
then last but definitely not least is
the most profitable scale ever trading
starting Capital can be anywhere from
100 bucks to $11,000 and the reason why
it could be so low is because with
trading currencies many Brokers give you
the option to leverage trade where you
can actually leverage your money a lot
more than you could in any other
business or any other Market your margin
is 100% because whatever you make on
trading is whatever you keep what you
need in order to actually start making
money is nothing other than yourself and
a strategy the risk associated with it
tend to be low and on the medium side
simply because you pre-calculate every
trade before you you execute it and
before you execute it you know exactly
how much you are going to be risking so
you know exactly what you can possibly
lose and the
scalability very very high and at this
point you're probably even asking if
this is for you and could it even happen
to you well it happened to Ricky Ricky
has a family he's a realtor he had very
little time in order for him to access
trading nonetheless practice and learn a
strategy after Ricky being part of the
community and learning the strategy and
just under 6 months Ricky has been able
to surpass his income as a full-time
realtor now he's able to leverage his
time spending more time with his family
making more money from Trading and not
leaving his passion as being a realtor
so he's able to make the deals that he
really wants to in real estate make the
amount of money that he wants from
Trading and spend all the time he wants
with his family and his kids and I know
this might sound crazy right now but I
can almost guarantee you that you will
not lose money with this business model
probably wondering how if I have to
trade I have to put money in the market
well before you enter any trade into the
market you have to learn how to
pre-calculate your risk on your account
and when you pre-calculate your risk you
know exactly how much you're going to be
losing and then how much you're going to
be gaining if for example let's say you
have a 50% win rate which is very below
average in the industry say out of 10
trades let's say you lose Lo six trades
and then you win four you would think
that if you lose more than you win then
you would be unprofitable and you would
lose money that's actually completely
false because every single time that you
would lose you would lose minus one for
example now you're minus 6 and every
single time you win it's times 2 so here
you have 2 4 6 8 you have just made back
with four wins the six losses and and
you are still profitable two points that
my friends is called risk to reward and
profitable risk management managing this
is what has led me to make millions in
the markets and constantly stay
profitable there's times where I have
lost seven trades in a row and just
winning three has made back those losses
and left me in Far More profit now all
this might sound very cool but you're
probably like Alex I have a full-time
job I still go to school I might even
have a family that I have to take care
of how am I going to be able to fit my
schedule to learning this new skill set
well truthfully it's actually far more
simple than you can imagine since you
don't have to manage a team see you
don't have to hire people you don't have
to create systems you don't have to
speak to anybody you know when you're
available and you know when you have
free time and in that free time you have
to dedicate anywhere from 1 to 2 hours
hours every single day without stopping
to learn the skill set and watch the
markets the secret is in the pudding you
have to watch the markets in order fore
to know what's going to happen next in
the markets now does it mean you have to
be glued to the screen in order for you
to actually make money but you have to
have this connection with the markets
where you see it for a long periods of
time where you start to enter this flow
and you start to understand the markets
where then you can start executing a
strategy you won't need to spend any
more than 1 to two Max 3 hours every
single day in order for you to learn
this skill set in under six months for
example let's just take Mike again he
started knowing absolutely nothing of
trading in the middle of Alberta Canada
where nobody there really knows how to
even access the internets and when how
to nonetheless even trade he knew
nothing about trading and in his first
three months he turned $8,000 into
$120,000
by him simply being available learning
the skill set and executing the strategy
while nobody in his family believed in
him and nobody in his family even knew
what he was doing and as I've met
thousands of Traders around the world
I've met all different types of Traders
I've met moms I've met dads I've met
teenagers I've met construction workers
teachers lawyers doctors scientists I've
met all different types of people people
that were even homeless that made it out
of being homeless Hess ended up becoming
a profitable Trader which is actually
one of my top students all you simply
have to do is have anywhere from 1 to 2
hours available every single day and
commit to it there's no way around the
success unless you commit you have to be
ready to put in the time and actually
practice and learn this skill set and if
you follow the strategy to the te it is
impossible to not get results because
you're following a proven strategy that
has made money for thousands of Traders
and for me personally the best analogy
that I can give for this is I'm going to
give you a very successful gym routine
for you to get sixpack apps and you can
go to the gym but if you just go to the
gym and you walk around and you just
stay on your phone and don't work out
there's nothing else that I can do for
you I gave you the routine now you have
to go out there and execute it just
because you went to the gym doesn't mean
you're going to get abs because you just
went there just because you sit in front
of the computer and look at the markets
doesn't mean you're going to make money
you have to actually get the strategy
and go and execute it and there's a very
big Superstition on people constantly
being concerned on when is the right
time to buy when is the right time to
sell obviously that is the secret and
people think it's the hardest part what
if I told you that this is actually the
easiest part and it is the part that
takes the longest for Traders to
understand 90% of my time in the markets
consists of doing nothing is waiting for
my strategy to be met and and for then
for me to go ahead and execute the
strategy I'm simply sitting on my hands
waiting for the market to give me an
opportunity and as soon as I get it I
execute it you really don't have to do
anything else other than just wait
patience pays in the markets now you're
probably wondering what happens if you
don't have any money to get started well
I'm going to be completely honest you
need some type of money in order for you
to make money in the markets you can't
make money out of thin air you have to
have a couple hundred bucks to get
started and there's two ways you can go
about it you can either one take a prop
firm challenge which they put your skill
set to the test if you pass their
challenge they will fund you money they
keep a certain percentage of the profits
and then you keep the others or you can
go a personal route which on the
personal route you get your money you
put it into a broker you get access to
higher amounts of Leverage and you can
scale that money a lot faster they're
both completely different Journeys I
personally have been on both and I like
the personal account better because you
make your own rules you don't have to be
following the strict rules that these
prop fir challenges make prop fir is
great but I would go personal all day so
now at this point you know exactly what
you need in order for you to go and
execute a trade in the market with a
high probability trade setup the first
is going to be the trend you need to be
trading with the market if it's going to
the upside or if it's going to the
downside you never want to trade against
it second is you you want to make sure
you have a very precise and key area of
Interest without a key area of Interest
even the best trend can't save you third
as soon as you're at that area of
interest because if you're not at one
you cannot then go to the next step once
you have that area of interest you can
then wait and apply a very specific and
strategic entry signal that will then
allow you to know exactly where you're
going to get out if you're wrong and
where you're going to get out if you're
right you pre-calculate how much you're
going to risk and you calculate how much
you're going to gain and then the last
step which is by far the most important
is sitting on your hands making sure
that you're only accessing the markets
when it is the right time staying true
to these rules and sticking to them and
not changing them for anything I get it
it's very tempting since the market is
available
24/7 and it's available at all times of
the day you want to enter it at all
times of the day but just because it's
available 24/7 doesn't mean you should
be entering it 24/7 so if you're able to
follow these steps precisely without
failing at any of them probably
wondering how much money can you make
well the sky is really the limit but if
I were to set some hardcore examples on
some numbers they're going to be the
ones that follows now these examples
vary on whether you're on a prop firm
account or on a personal account if you
have access to the figures that I'm
going to be breaking down down below by
means please go do it on your own
personal account you keep more of your
money and if you don't you go ahead and
you take a prop from account prop from
accounts can vary anywhere from $20 all
the way up to
$500 and with something as little as
$100 you can get access to a $110,000
challenge which once you pass that
challenge you then keep 70% of the
profits you make on this $10,000 account
so if you follow follow all of these
steps you can make an average of
anywhere from 8 to 12% in one single
given month just risking 1% now I need
to play Devil's out ofate here and give
you guys a realistic scenario on a very
low case I personally myself do not risk
1% I'm risking anywhere from 5 to 6 to
7% per trades simply because I am okay
with it and I want to educate you as a
potential beginner Trader or even
intermediate to be very conservative at
the start start risking 1% and 2% and
then you scale over time but I'm going
to do the mature thing and do these
calculations based off of 1% obviously
if you double the risk so do these
numbers if you triple so do these
numbers as well so let's say you start
off with a $110,000 account which would
cost you $100 if you go take a prop from
challenge let's say you make make an
average of 10% which is very doable
risking 1% per trade you would then keep
a 70% profit of that after the profit
split with the propit fir making you
$700 within that one given month now
keep in mind if you do this on your
personal account you keep 100% of those
profits but now on the same exact
$10,000 account let's say you up your
risk to 5% per trade so now on this
exact same example on the $10,000
account let's say you upped your risk to
what I do let's just say 5% for example
you could have made an easy 25 to 40% on
that exact same account on that one
given month taking the exact same trades
just risking 5% instead of one where
then you could have been making anywhere
from $2500 to
$3,500 by just passing a prop from
challenge that is worth
$100 now obviously you can do this on
bigger figures like 50,000 and $100,000
where you can easily be making on a
$50,000 challenge anywhere from $5,000
to $15,000 risking the exact same
percentage taking the exact same trades
the only thing that changes is the size
of your account meaning which is the
amount of money you have access into the
market if you don't have all this money
on a personal account believe me I did
not have it when I got started working
at Dunkin Donuts I went a prop firm
account I passed your challenge es and I
acquired
$300,000 in funding and I ended up
making 10% on just one given month on
that $300,000 account I received the
profit split of over
$25,000 so the exact same percentage
that you could be making on a $10,000
account you could be on a $300,000
account and it just cost you
$700 now there's many prop firms
throughout the whole entire industry
make sure you do your due diligence
properly
the goal is to make as much money as you
can from the prop firms and then you put
it into your own personal account and
the reason behind that is because you
keep 100% of the profits that you make
on your personal account on a prop firm
you constantly have to be splitting with
the firm as you can see you can make a
lot of money and these are just very
very very below average examples just so
I keep it very realistic with you using
a very small percentage and I don't know
if these sound like big or small figures
to you but truthfully in the market they
really are you could take someone like
faka where he made
$90,000 in one single month in trading
after learning the strategy for 6 months
to somebody that did not have great
English and figured out a way how to
dedicate the time learn the strategy and
he nearly made six figures in one single
month so the figures that I was just
giving you an example are very below
average and very realistic for you to
obtain making six figures in a month is
not far-fetched or you can take someone
like hakee for example where he was
living in Jamaica and he didn't have
super big aspirations of making millions
and he managed to make in one single
year $40,000 from Trading alone he said
when I spoke to him in the podcast that
that went very far in Jamaica for him
and he was able to live the life that he
wanted and I don't know if this is going
to change or better your situation but
hakee is making an extra 3,300 a month
so imagine that in your situation right
now might mean a lot might mean a little
but all that by simply dedicating
anywhere from 1 to 2 hours every single
day for the next 6 months to me when I
was working at deckin Donuts that was a
great deal and I'm not sure if you're
wondering this at this point or not but
you're probably asking yourself if
you're so successful Alex you've made
millions in the markets why are you
making these hourlong videos why do you
have a community if you're so rich off
trading why well truthfully at the age
of 24 I've achieved many things that
people my age have never even thought of
and truthfully I did it all by myself
and being at the top by yourself really
is lonely so I decided to change my
priorities in life and I said that it's
better for me to change lives all around
me instead of it being off for me and
being super selfish I decided to go out
there and provide as much free value as
I possibly can which it can potentially
change the course course of somebody's
life completely and I have a goal that's
for my students in 2025 collectively for
all of them to make $5 million in just
this year alone we do podcasts every
single week and we track the results
every single day and collectively adding
this to a meter which I am very sure
we're going to hit that goal for this
year and also one of the deep reasons on
why I do this is I remember working at
Dunkin Donuts and I was trying to figure
out how to get out of this job trying a
bunch of different Ventures just trying
different ways on how to make money
online and everybody that was online
just wanted to make money off of you for
being online there was nobody out there
doing something free for the community
there was nobody out there actually
providing real value all the information
was scattered all over the place and
truthfully I didn't learn much off of
one single person I had to get different
pieces of knowledge and start piecing
everything together that's why my first
2 and 1/2 years of my journey were
brutal they were to the point where I
had no money left and I had to ask my
parents for money so I can get back into
trading and not give up on what I wanted
to do it got to the point where I didn't
know when I was going to be successful
but I was so deep into the journey that
I simply had no other choice but
achieving it I was so invested and I had
dedicated so much time that I lost all
of my friends all of my family members
stopped believing in me it was just me
and the charts and I was not going to
let a computer beat me so I decided to
put my head down learn from my mistakes
and get to the point where I am now and
after reaching a certain level of
success so fast your priorities change
in life they really do and you start
looking at life differently and you
start taking on new challenges now it's
not about how much money can I make but
it's about how much money can I get
someone to make because if I'm entering
a trade why shouldn't you doesn't affect
me if you make more money than me
doesn't affect me if you don't make
money at all the markets are there the
opportunity is there and it's for
everyone's grabbing and I've gra and
I've gotten great amount of passion
changing people's Liv and showing the
Simplicity of this opportunity and the
impact that it can have in people's
lives and I'm going to be honest I did
not start this journey by myself I
started with two of my high school
friends with which I thought they were
my closest friends and later throughout
the journey they ended up not believing
in it at all and they just couldn't
handle the pressure and I wasn't going
to go down without a fight so I kept
fighting by myself and I ended up
meeting other people that were in that
same Journey just fighting trying to
figure out a way on how to become
successful all of us just putting money
into the pop figuring out how to make a
profitable strategy and the more money
we would put in the more time we would
put in the more money we would get out
and all of us had this aha moment and we
were figuring out how to actually become
successful and make money in the markets
therefore I learned a profitable
strategy that took Me 2 and 1/2 years
and thousands of dollars loss
relationships so much stress that I
thought I was going to lose my hair as a
1920 year-old and as soon as I acquired
this skill set I was not going to let
anybody access it for free as soon as I
started Living a lifestyle buying cool
things doing what I wanted then all my
friends wanted to come back and asked
for help and for me to teach them how to
do it at the beginning I did it and I
felt guilty if I didn't it didn't feel
fair that I learned something and now it
makes me get access to money so easy and
I felt for it I would go and I would
help them but you know what they were
ungrateful because they weren't
investing anything other than time and
to them their time is valued at $10 $15
an hour so they didn't care about losing
time learning something it wasn't a big
deal but to me it was because my time is
very valuable now that I've learned this
skill set so I no longer help people
that aren't willing to invest into
themselves and value their time in order
for them to become successful and
actually learn how to make money and
I've seen this over the years the more
the people invest the more committed
they get the more committed they get the
more money they ultimately make you need
to become a Trader in order to make
profits like a Trader you simply can't
just think because you show up that
you're going to get the same results as
somebody that has changed their whole
entire life routine around just becoming
a Trader that person that changes
everything for this gets everything they
should from this and I've done hundreds
of different YouTube videos showcasing
many different types of ways on how to
simplify Trading so people can actually
understand it on one simple spot because
when I got started trading I was
searching YouTube endlessly not finding
organized content I have organized
everything that people need to know
right here off of my YouTube but for
some reason people never really actually
make tens of thousands even hundreds of
thousands dollars from YouTube and they
don't make this amount of money because
they lack discipline they lack
consistency and they lack accountability
now I want to see if you're different I
have this 4our tutorial video where I
teach you trading from zero all the way
up to 100 I'm talking everything this
video took me 6 hours to record without
stopping and we managed to cut it down
to 4 hours I want to see if you're
different are you going to lack
commitment not be dedicated and not hold
yourself accountable or you going to go
watch this 4our video that's going to
teach you trading from 0 to 100
completely for free and because now that
you know that this is the most
profitable skill ever compared to any
other different business model you're
just one simple step away you're only
one simple step away from Deep diving on
how this strategy actually works why
would you go on the internet and search
for other different opportunities you
understand that this is it you're just
simply one click away and I can almost
guarantee you that in the first 10
minutes of you watching this 4-Hour
video you're going to learn something
something that you can apply to your
trading immediately for you to be able
to start trading and making money with
it so with that being said Thank you
guys very much for watching this video
make sure to hit that like And subscribe
on this video and I want to see What
You're Made Of I want to see what you're
about cuz if you're really different
from the other people you won't stop
here you've made it this far go watch
this video and I'll see you there now